

MD YOUSUF JAMIL

Front-end Developer yousufjamil733@gmail.com

I completed my BSc degree in Computer Science from American International University-Bangladesh (AIUB) in 2018.. I'm interested in the Front-End web development role with my favorite technologies. I write code using HTML, CSS, JS, and Bootstrap for the majority of my projects. I have over one year of experience in front-end website development and WordPress theme customization at Sunshine IT.

Therefore, my goal is to combine all the skills and work in a responsible position where I can use my potential, creativity, skills, and practical experience to contribute successfully to the organization by developing my career.

Website: https://yousufj733.github.io/yousuf-jamil

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/md-yousuf-jamil-3a529313a

GitHub: https://github.com/yousufj733
Fiverr: https://www.fiverr.com/w3jamil

Cell: 01745-020001

Email: yousufjamil733@gmail.com

Skype: yousufj95

Address: Dhaka, Bangladesh.

EXPERIENCE:

Front-End Developer at Sunshine IT (Oct 2021 - Nov 2022)

- Implement web applications with modern technologies and client requirements.
- Building one of the most challenging front-end applications.
- Maintain responsive layout to perfect in any device.
- Solve front-end related any problem instantly.
- Maintenance code format style best ways and follow the reusable structure.
- Communicate with our team to produce client project development.

Jr. Executive at Digicon Technologies Ltd (Mar 2019 - Aug 2021)

- Identify customer needs, clarify information and provide solutions.
- Provided prompt customer service in the opening of new accounts and helped Maintain sales culture
- Manage social media, email & web chat.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND:

American International University, Bangladesh.

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science (2013-2018)

CGPA: 2.86 (Out of 4)

Agriculture University College, Mymensingh.

HIGHER SECONDARY CERTIFICATE (2011)

Science

GPA: 4.70 (out of 5)

Pre-Cadet High school, Mymensingh

SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE (2009)

Science

GPA: 5.00 (out of 5)

CERTIFICATION - WORKSHOP - SEMINARS:

- completed CCNA Course from AIUB
- Participated in a programing contest organized by the Department of CS
- Attended seminar on Network Security also organized by CS Department

REFERENCE:

ABHIJIT BHOWMIK
Sr. Assistant Professor,
Department of Computer Science, AIUB.
Email- abhijit@aiub.edu